<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dataroot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="teams.xsd"
    generated="2011-11-05T23:09:59">

<person>
    <name>About - Futbol Club Barcelona, commonly referred to as Barcelona and
        colloquially known as Barça, is a professional football club based in Barcelona,
        Catalonia, Spain, that competes in La Liga, the top flight of Spanish football. </name>
    <fact>Barcelona currently have over 259 million followers across various social media platforms, with Facebook and Instagram accounting for more than 200 million. That makes Barcelona the football club with the second-highest social media following, narrowly overtaken by Real Madrid who have over 262 million.</fact>
    <networth>Net Worth - $2.5 Billion</networth>

    <history>The history of Barcelona has often been political.
        Though it was a club created and run by foreigners, Barcelona gradually became a club associated with Catalan values.
        In Spain's transition to autocracy in 1925, Catalonia became increasingly hostile towards the central government in Madrid. The hostility enhanced Barcelona's image as a focal point for Catalonism,
        and when Francisco Franco banned the use of the Catalan language, the stadium of Barcelona became one of the few places the people could express their dissatisfaction. The Spanish transition to democracy in 1978 has not dampened the club's image of Catalan pride.
        In the 2000s and 2010s – a period of sporting success in the club and an increased focus on Catalan players – club officials have been openly faithful to historic club commitment to the defense of the country, democracy,
        freedom of expression and the right to decide, and have condemns any action that may impede the full exercise of these rights.</history>


    <image>barcelona</image>

    <url>https://www.fcbarcelona.com/en/</url>
</person>
    <person>
        <name>About - Paris Saint-Germain Football Club, commonly referred to as Paris Saint-Germain,
            Paris, Paris SG or simply PSG is a professional football club based in Paris, France.
            They compete in Ligue 1, the top division of French football </name>

        <fact>In 2011, Qatar Sports Investments took a 70% share in PSG, becoming their only shareholder just one year later. Five years later, the club was known for having the fourth-highest revenue in the entire football world at nearly 481 million euros</fact>

        <history>Paris Saint-Germain Football Club was founded in August 1970 after the merger of Paris Football Club and Stade Saint-Germain. PSG made an immediate impact, winning promotion to Division 1 and claiming the Division 2 title in their first season. Their momentum was soon checked, however, and the club split in 1972. Paris FC remained in the top flight, while PSG were administratively relegated to Division 3. Following back-to-back promotions, PSG quickly returned to the premier division in 1974 and moved into the Parc des Princes.

            The club's first trophies arrived in the 1980s. Steered by players such as Safet Sušić, Luis Fernandez and Dominique Rocheteau,
            the Parisians claimed two consecutive French Cup titles in 1982 and 1983 followed by their maiden league championship in 1986, after which they went into decline.
            But a takeover by television giants Canal+ in 1991 revitalised PSG. Led by David Ginola,
            George Weah and Raí, the club won nine trophies and reached five consecutive European semi-finals during the 1990s. Most notably,
            Paris claimed a second league title in 1994 and its crowning glory, the UEFA Cup Winners' Cup in 1996 with legend Luis Fernandez now as coach.</history>

        <networth>Net Worth - $21.5 Billion</networth>

        <image>psg</image>

        <url>https://en.psg.fr/</url>
    </person>
    <person>
        <name>About - Chelsea Football Club is an English professional football club based in Fulham, West London.
            Founded in 1905, they play their home games at Stamford Bridge. The club competes in the Premier League, the top division of English football.
            They won their first major honour, the League championship, in 1955 </name>

        <fact>Chelsea took a giant step forward by donning numbered kits at an age when it was unheard of. The Premier League giants first wore numbered kits during their match against Swansea City back in 1928. They became the first clubs, along with Arsenal, to initiate the tradition of numbered kits</fact>

        <history>In 1904, Gus Mears acquired the Stamford Bridge athletics stadium in Fulham with the aim of turning it into a football ground. An offer to lease it to nearby Fulham F.C. was turned down, so Mears opted to found his own club to use the stadium. As there was already a team named Fulham in the borough, the name of the adjacent borough of Chelsea was chosen for the new club; names like Kensington FC, Stamford Bridge FC and London FC were also considered.[10] Chelsea F.C. was founded on 10 March 1905 at The Rising Sun pub (now The Butcher's Hook),[2][11] opposite the present-day main entrance to the ground on Fulham Road, and were elected to the Football League shortly afterwards.

            Chelsea won promotion to the First Division in their second season, and yo-yoed between the
            First and Second Divisions in their early years. They reached the 1915 FA Cup Final, where they lost to Sheffield United at Old Trafford,
            and finished third in the First Division in 1920, the club's best league campaign to that point.[12] Chelsea had a reputation for signing star players[13] and attracted large crowds.
            The club had the highest average attendance in English football in ten separate seasons[14] including 1907–08,[15] 1909–10,[16] 1911–12,[17] 1912–13,[18] 1913–14[19] and 1919–20.[20][21]
            They were FA Cup semi-finalists in 1920 and 1932 and remained in the First Division throughout the 1930s,
            but success eluded the club in the inter-war years.</history>

        <networth>Net Worth - $2.5 Billion</networth>

        <image>chelsea</image>

        <url>https://www.chelseafc.com/en</url>
    </person>
    <person>

        <name>About - Football Club Internazionale Milano, commonly referred to as Internazionale or simply Inter,
            and known as Inter Milan in English-speaking countries,
            is an Italian professional football club based in Milan, Lombardy </name>

        <fact>FC Inter Milan won with a whopping 3-0 making them the FIFA Club World Cup Champions of the year 2010. The goal scorers that made all of this possible were Jonathan Biabiany, Goran Pandev and Samuel Eto’o with the last goal scored in the 85th minute.</fact>

        <history>The club was founded on 9 March 1908 as Football Club Internazionale, following the schism with the Milan Cricket and Football Club (now AC Milan). The name of the club derives from the wish of its founding members to accept foreign players without limits as well as Italians.

            The club won its first championship in 1910 and its second in 1920. The captain and coach of the first championship winning team was Virgilio Fossati, who was later killed in battle while serving in the Italian army during World War I. In 1922, Inter was at risk of relegation to the second division, but they remained in the top league after winning two play-offs.

            Six years later, during the Fascist era, the club was forced to merge with the Unione Sportiva Milanese and was renamed Società Sportiva Ambrosiana.[17]
            During the 1928–29 season, the team wore white jerseys with a red cross emblazoned on it; the jersey's design was inspired by the flag and coat of arms of the city of Milan.
            In 1929, the new club chairman Oreste Simonotti changed the club's name to Associazione Sportiva Ambrosiana and restored the previous black-and-blue jerseys, however supporters continued to call the team Inter,
            and in 1931 new chairman Pozzani caved in to shareholder pressure and changed the name to Associazione Sportiva Ambrosiana-Inter.Their first Coppa Italia (Italian Cup) was won in 1938–39, led by the iconic Giuseppe Meazza,
            after whom the San Siro stadium is officially named. A fifth championship followed in 1940, despite Meazza incurring an injury. After the end of World War II the club regained its original name, winning its sixth championship in 1953 and its seventh in 1954.</history>

        <networth>Net Worth - $2.5 Billion</networth>

        <image>inter_milan</image>

        <url>https://www.inter.it/en</url>
    </person>
    <person>

        <name>About - Juventus Football Club, colloquially known as Juve, is a professional football club based in Turin, Piedmont, Italy,
            that competes in the Serie A,
            the top tier of the Italian football league system </name>

        <fact>In 1985, Juventus became the first club in the history of European football to have won all three major UEFA club competitions and first Italian to do so. Juventus is also the only team in the world to have won all official international cups and championships.
        </fact>

        <history>Juventus were founded as Sport-Club Juventus in late 1897 by pupils from the Massimo d'Azeglio Lyceum school in Turin, among them the brothers Eugenio and Enrico Canfari,[28]
            but were renamed as Foot-Ball Club Juventus two years later.[29] The club joined the Italian Football Championship in 1900. Juventus played their first match in club's history on 11 March 1900,
            in a 1–0 defeat against Torinese.[30] In 1904, the businessman Ajmone-Marsan revived the finances of the football club Juventus, making it also possible to transfer the training field from piazza d'armi to the more appropriate
            Velodrome Umberto I. During this period, the team wore a pink and black kit. Juventus first won the league championship in 1905 while playing at their Velodrome Umberto I ground. By this time the club colours had changed to black
            and white stripes, inspired by English side Notts County.[31]
            There was a split at the club in 1906, after some of the staff considered moving Juve out of Turin.[29] President Alfred Dick[g]
            was unhappy with this and left with some prominent players to found FBC Torino which in turn spawned the Derby della Mole.[32] Juventus spent much of this period steadily rebuilding after the split,
            surviving the First World War.[31]</history>

        <networth>Net Worth - $2.5 Billion</networth>

        <image>juventus</image>

        <url>https://www.juventus.com/en/</url>
    </person>
    <person>

        <name>About - Liverpool Football Club is a professional football club based in Liverpool, England.
            The club competes in the Premier League, the top tier of English football.
            Founded in 1892, the club joined the Football League the following year and has played its home games at Anfield since its formation </name>

        <fact>Liverpool FC’s youngest ever starting line-up has been recorded as 19 years and 182 days – a young squad played in the League Cup against Aston Villa in December 2019 due to the first team’s commitments playing in the Club World Cup tournament</fact>

        <history>Liverpool F.C. was founded following a dispute between the Everton committee and John Houlding, club president and fact of the land at Anfield.
            After eight years at the stadium, Everton relocated to Goodison Park in 1892 and Houlding founded Liverpool F.C. to play at Anfield.[3] Originally named "Everton F.C. and Athletic Grounds Ltd"
            (Everton Athletic for short), the club became Liverpool F.C. in March 1892 and gained official recognition three months later, after The Football Association refused to recognise the club as Everton.[4]
            Liverpool played their first match on 1 September 1892, a pre-season friendly match against Rotherham Town, which they won 7–1. The team Liverpool fielded against Rotherham was composed entirely of Scottish players – the players who came from Scotland to play in England in those days were known as the Scotch Professors. Manager John McKenna had recruited the players after a scouting trip to Scotland – so they became known as the "team of Macs".[5] The team won the Lancashire League in its debut season and joined the Football League Second Division at the start of the 1893–94 season. After the club was promoted to the First Division in 1896, Tom Watson was appointed manager. He led Liverpool to its first league title in 1901, before winning it again in 1906.[6]
            Liverpool reached its first FA Cup Final in 1914, losing 1–0 to Burnley. It won consecutive League championships in 1922 and 1923, but did not win another trophy until the 1946–47 season,
            when the club won the First Division for a fifth time under the control of ex-West Ham United centre half George Kay.[7] Liverpool suffered its second Cup Final defeat in 1950, playing against Arsenal.[8]
            The club was relegated to the Second Division in the 1953–54 season.</history>

        <networth>Net Worth - $2.5 Billion</networth>

        <image>liverpool</image>

        <url>https://www.liverpoolfc.com/</url>
    </person>
    <person>

        <name>About - Manchester City Football Club are an English football club based in Manchester that competes in the Premier League,
            the top flight of English football. Founded in 1880 as St.
            Mark's, they became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894</name>

        <fact>Manchester City is one of four clubs that are part of the City Football Group. City have an affiliation with Melbourne City, Yokohama F. Marinos and New York City.</fact>

        <history>City gained their first honours by winning the Second Division in 1899; with it came promotion to the highest level in English football, the First Division. They went on to claim their first major honour on 23 April 1904, beating Bolton Wanderers 1–0 at Crystal Palace to win the FA Cup; the Blues narrowly missed out on a League and Cup double that season after finishing runners-up in the league campaign, but they still became the first club in Manchester to win a major honour.[13] In the seasons following the FA Cup triumph, the club was dogged by allegations of financial irregularities, culminating in the suspension of seventeen players in 1906, including captain Billy Meredith, who subsequently moved across town to Manchester United.[14] A fire at Hyde Road destroyed the main stand in 1920, and in 1923 the club moved to their new purpose-built stadium at Maine Road in Moss Side.[15]

            A group of thirteen men, eleven in association football attire typical of the early twentieth century, and two in suits. A trophy sits in front of them.
            The Manchester City team which won the FA Cup in 1903–04.
            In the 1930s, Manchester City reached two consecutive FA Cup finals, losing to Everton in 1933, before claiming the Cup by beating Portsmouth in 1934.[16]
            During the 1934 run, the club broke the record for the highest home attendance of any club in English football history, as 84,569 fans packed Maine Road for a sixth-round FA Cup tie against Stoke City –
            a record which stood until 2016.[17][18] The club won the First Division title for the first time in 1937, but were relegated the following season, despite scoring more goals than any other team in the division.[19]
            Twenty years later, a City team inspired by a tactical system known as the Revie Plan reached consecutive FA Cup finals again, in 1955 and 1956; just as in the 1930s,
            they lost the first one, to Newcastle United, and won the second. The 1956 final, in which the Blues defeated Birmingham City 3–1, saw City goalkeeper Bert Trautmann continuing to play
            on after unknowingly breaking his neck.[20]</history>

        <networth>Net Worth - $2.5 Billion</networth>

        <image>manchester_city</image>

        <url>https://www.mancity.com/</url>
    </person>
    <person>

        <name>About - Manchester United Football Club, commonly referred to as Man United, or simply United,
            is a professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England. The club competes in the Premier League,
            the top division in the English football league system </name>

        <fact>No one has won more Premier League titles than Manchester United.  Red Devils have won 13 times out of the 28 seasons played so far. But Manchester also leads the tournament’s historical table in terms of most wins, most goals, and most points won.</fact>

        <history>Manchester United was formed in 1878 as Newton Heath LYR Football Club by the Carriage and Wagon department of the Lancashire and Yorkshire Railway (LYR) depot at Newton Heath.[16]
            The team initially played games against other departments and railway companies, but on 20 November 1880, they competed in their first recorded match; wearing the colours of the railway company – green and gold –
            they were defeated 6–0 by Bolton Wanderers' reserve team.[17] By 1888, the club had become a founding member of The Combination, a regional football league.
            Following the league's dissolution after only one season, Newton Heath joined the newly formed Football Alliance, which ran for three seasons before being merged with The Football League.
            This resulted in the club starting the 1892–93 season in the First Division, by which time it had become independent of the railway company and dropped the "LYR" from its name.[16] After two seasons,
            the club was relegated to the Second Division.[16]</history>

        <networth>Net Worth - $2.5 Billion</networth>

        <image>manchester_united</image>

        <url>https://www.manutd.com/</url>
    </person>
</dataroot>
